<corpus>
	
	<corpusID>corpus:audioID:IRCAM:SyncOccur:2012:version1.0</corpusID>
	<version>1.0</version>
	<release>2012-11-30</release>
	<author>Mathieu Ramona</author>
	<contact>mathieu.ramona.pro@gmail.com</contact>
	<source>http://www.mathieuramona.com/wp/syncoccur-corpus</source>
	<institution>IRCAM</institution>
	
	<raw>
		<definition>
			<id>a13</id>
			<type>sampled</type>
			<number>10000 pairs</number>
			<sampling>Detected by the occurrence synchronization algorithm detailed in M. Ramona and G. Peeters, "Automatic alignment of audio occurrences: application to the verification and synchronization of audio fingerprinting annotation," in Proc. DAFX '11, 2011, pp. 429-436.</sampling>
			<source>French broadcast radio</source>
		</definition>
		<media>
			<encoding>MPEG-4 AAC</encoding>
			<bitrate>96</bitrate>
			<channels>mono</channels>
		</media>
	</raw>
	
	<annotations>
		<origin>
			<id>b15</id>
			<type>manual</type>
		</origin>
		<definitions>
			<concepts>
				Each pair of audio samples contain two occurrences of the same musical track that are perfectly synchronized, but submitted to varying audio processes.
			</concepts>
			<rules>
				A XML file describes all pairs.
				The first version is automatically generated.
				Next versions are manually corrected.
				If the two samples contain different musical tracks or different edits, or are not synchronized, it should be corrected.
				If one sample contains additional noise (e.g. spoken voice added to the music), it should be corrected.
			</rules>
		</definitions>
		<quality>
			<annotators>
				Collaborative. Researchers, users of the corpus.
			</annotators>
			<reliability>
				All corrections are checked and validated by the creator of the corpus (Mathieu Ramona).
			</reliability>
		</quality>
		<tools>
			Any audio player (stereo version combining both samples is provided).
		</tools>
	</annotations>

	<storage>
		<audio>
			Each audio pair is provided with a unique item index.
			The "_stream" suffixed file contains the occurence cut from the test audio stream.
			The "_scaled" suffixed file contains the source item scaled to match synchroniously with the other file.
			The "_mix"    suffixed file contains the stereo mix of both audio chunks to assess their synchronicity.
		</audio>
		<annotation>
			annote.xml: a global XML file on a GIT server contains the annotations (i.e. the possible corrections) for all items.
		</annotation>
	</storage>
	
</corpus>
